--- 1. Student can get available exams ---
Available exams count: 10 Titles: [
  'Available Exam',
  'Submit Test Exam',
  'Available Exam',
  'Exam 1787856976079',
  'test  2',
  'test',
  'In Progress Exam',
  'Submit Test Exam',
  'Answer Test Exam',
  'Available Exam'
]

--- 2. Student cannot see inactive exams ---
Includes draft exam? false

--- 3. Admin is blocked from student exam routes ---
Admin access status: 403

--- 4. Student can view a single available exam ---
Success: true Exam ID: 240004

--- 9. Student cannot start an unavailable exam ---
Start draft status: 404 { success: false, message: 'Exam not found or unavailable' }

--- 5, 6, 7. Student starts an available exam ---
